Everyone loves a holiday!
人人都爱假期！
A little time off for some much-needed R & R can be exactly the thing to rejuvenate and refresh.
抽出一点时间来好好休息放松（R & R，即Rest and Relaxation），正是恢复活力、焕发精神的良方。
That said, if you're struggling to think of your next destination then look no further.
话虽如此，如果你正纠结于下一个目的地，那就别再犹豫了。
Don't waste time debating, let your blood decide.
不必浪费时间争论，让你的血脉来决定吧。
Everybody has a lineage.
每个人都有自己的家族谱系。
Recently, finding out more about our family origins has become popular.
近年来，探寻家族起源的风潮日渐盛行。
By the start of 2019, 26 million people had taken an ancestry DNA test at home, according to a report by MIT Technology Review.
据《麻省理工科技评论》报道，截至2019年初，已有2600万人在家中进行了祖先DNA检测。
They believe by 2021 this number will have risen to 100 million.
他们预计到2021年，这一数字将增至1亿。
This trend has been noticed by opportunistic travel operators.
精明的旅游运营商已经注意到了这一趋势。
Some are looking to provide a service that both allows people to trace their heritage - by literally going back to their roots - and travel to the destinations where their ancestors originated from.
一些运营商希望提供这样一种服务：既让人们能够追溯自己的家族传承——真正回到“根”之所在——又能前往祖先的发源地旅行。
Airbnb, an online lodging marketplace, recently partnered with 23andMe, a DNA testing and analysis company, to offer recommendations that encourage travellers to walk in the footsteps of their forefathers.
在线住宿平台爱彼迎（Airbnb）最近与DNA检测分析公司23andMe合作，推出旅行推荐服务，鼓励旅行者追随祖先的足迹。
And they aren't the only ones.
而这样做的并非只有他们一家。
The Shelbourne hotel in Dublin has its own 'genealogy butler'.
都柏林的谢尔伯恩酒店（The Shelbourne）拥有专属的“谱系管家”。
Hellen Kelly offers consultations to help guests trace their Irish line of descent using official records.
海伦·凯利提供咨询服务，帮助客人通过官方记录追溯自己的爱尔兰血统。
This allows them to 'fill in the blanks of their Irish ancestry', she told Good Morning America.
她在接受《早安美国》采访时表示，这能让客人“填补爱尔兰家族谱系中的空白”。
The Conte Club, a luxury travel company, offers custom itineraries based on DNA tests.
高端旅游公司孔特俱乐部（The Conte Club）提供基于DNA检测的定制旅行路线。
'These experiences are about delving deeper into who we really are,' says Conte Club CEO Rebecca Fielding in an article in the Condé Nast Traveller.
孔特俱乐部首席执行官丽贝卡·菲尔丁在《悦游》杂志的一篇文章中表示：“这些旅行体验旨在让我们更深入地探索真实的自我。
'It might be the most meaningful trip we can take.'
这可能是我们能进行的最有意义的旅行。”
So next time you think of going on vacation, why not take a DNA test first?
所以，下次计划度假时，不妨先做一次DNA检测？
Once you know how far your family has come, take the time to holiday back.
一旦你了解了家族的迁徙历程，就花点时间回到故土去度假吧。